Stacey Rhodes

Forward Thinking Accounting Professional With 10+ Years Experience, Expanding in the World of Databases.

San Antonio, TX 78239 staceyrhodes48_rsd@indeedemail.com 512.753.9105

Analytically driven professional who excels at prioritizing, completing multiple tasks simultaneously and following through to achieve project and company goals. My background consists of more than 10+ years in accounting, office management, and administrative roles. Currently, during my free time, I am expanding my knowledge in the area of databases.

#readytowork

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Enterprise Resource Planning Specialist

Southern Folger Detention Equipment - San Antonio, TX September 2019 to May 2020

- Project based position to move over data from an AS/400 to an ERP system. Developed training materials and trained company departments on the new system.
- Provides developmental, technical, and functional support in the areas of: ERP systems administration, problem solving, support, process mapping, system testing and development, security access, and training.
- Assists in developing procedures, and test procedures to ensure integrity of the ERP system and databases.
- Works as a system analyst with key personnel to help define user needs and develop data processing solutions.
- Assists controller with invoicing and budget management.

Financial Controller/ Office Manager

Advanced Wood Floors, LLC - San Antonio, TX October 2016 to April 2019

- Promoted from Administrative Assistant/Inventory Controller working side by side with President and VP/CFO.
- Generated and presented weekly update of accounts receivables and payables outlining profits/ losses and preparing year end accounts for tax filing.
- Reconciled banks on a daily basis and book inventory monthly with warehouse. Created better inventory tracking protocol and accounts payable systems.
- AR/AP and collections management. Job costing, working with proposals and contracts.
- Processed in-house and subcontractor payroll. Managed employee files, 401k, and insurances.
- Hiring, training and retaining skilled office staff.
- Resolved technical issues.

Manager/Personal Assistant

Scrubbin Troubles - San Antonio, TX January 2015 to January 2016

- Monitored work quality and provided training to employees.
- Budget management, payroll management, invoicing, and payment processing.
- Organizing, allocating, and purchase of all business supplies.
- Conducted face to face service estimates to acquire new clients.
- Created and maintained schedules for staff and clients.

Accounting Assistant to CFO/ Engineering Coordinator

Clark Construction - San Antonio, TX September 2015 to December 2015

- As a contract employee I analyzed, examined, and interpreted accounting records. Compiled financial information, reconciled reports, and financial data.
- Investigated and resolved discrepancies for 3 years worth of previous financial statements and vendor accounts while under tight deadlines.
- Researched and resolved billing and invoice errors. Processed an average of 100 invoices per day for a large scale organization.
- Created and compiled street data from Google Earth for engineers to use on bids. Organized, reviewed and made edits to contracts.

Bookkeeper/ US Trainer

Newalta Environmental - San Antonio, TX January 2014 to July 2015

- Collaborated with out of Country and US corporate business executives to resolve employee training issues, and trained employees per management requests.
- Researched and resolved collection and billing disputes. Opened and assigned new client accounts.
- Conducted month-end balance sheet reviews and reconciled variances in SAP.
- Coded the general ledger and balanced batch summary reports for verification and approval.
- Created, followed up on, and completed purchase orders in a timely manner.
- Maintained confidential employee files and processed employee payrolls.
- Assisted the branch manager with weekly and monthly expense forecasts, including any necessary recommended action required to manage costs and to stay on budget.

Park Manager

Eagleford RV Park - Gonzales, TX June 2013 to September 2013

- Created weekly and monthly accounting reports, presentations, and discussed marketing with owners.
- Created marketing initiatives, met with local business owners, and worked with the Chamber of Commerce to provide information and create awareness about the newly developed park.
- Welcomed new guests with park information and community activities. Generated guest invoices and processed payments. Provided guests with safety information
- Directed web developer with design and park information.

HR/ Residential Coordinator

D&S Community Services - Austin, TX October 2008 to May 2013

- Promoted from HR/Administrative Assistant and worked side by side with the Executive Director to manage 2 area offices.
- Processed payroll, managed personnel files, conducted home inspections, and managed insurances for 200+ employees.
- Resolved overtime issues reducing overtime by 97%.
- Trained and provided administrative and HR support to offices throughout the company.
- Completed annual state survey with 0 tags/citations on all personnel files, client banking information and home inspections.
- Managed 40 client accounts, deposited funds, distributed weekly allowances and reconciled accounts monthly in Quickbooks, and MS Money.

Education

Some College

Del Mar College - Corpus Christi, TX January 2004 to May 2004

High school or equivalent

Flour Bluff HS - Corpus Christi, TX May 2002 to May 2002

Skills

- Payroll
- ADP
- Quickbooks
- Scheduling
- · Problem solving
- Outlook
- Powerpoint
- Ms money
- SAP
- Pivot tables
- Self starter
- accounting
- Management
- Employee Relations
- Accounts Payable
- Financial Reporting
- Financial Analysis
- Accounts Receivable
- Research
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Office
- Training

Certifications and Licenses

Certified Notary Public

November 2018 to November 2022

Currently certified in Texas.

Additional Information

Skills

SAP, QuickBooks MS Money, Time Clock Systems, Project Management Excel/Pivot tables/V-Lookup, PowerPoint Expert, Calendars/Scheduling Microsoft Office Expert, Payroll Systems, ADP, Office Equipment Outlook Expert, Epicor

Qualities

Creative Problem Solving Attention to detail Self Starter Great Work Ethic